Yes sir, how can I help you?
I made a reservation.
Last name?
Moore.
Okay. I just need your ID and your method of payment.
Okay.
Here’s my ID.
Any pets with you?
No pets.
And credit card's okay?
Mm-hmm. (affirmative)
Cell phone number?
325-555-5555.
And its just for ... two nights.
Two nights. Right.
All right. Is this, would you like one key or two?
Just one key is okay.
Okay. Can I have your initial everywhere that's highlighted.
It's gonna be for the rate and non-smoking policy.
Sign at the X and then answer the highlighted questions as well.
Okay.
And check out will be Tuesday before 12.
Breakfast is from 6 to 9, during the week.
Free wifi, no passcode.
The elevator down, will be down the hall to left on the first floor.
And pool closes at ten.
Okay. And what kind of food do you have for breakfast?
Uhm, we have the pop breakfast
so it's the sausage, eggs, pastries, gravy and then the waffle machine
and then the standard continental.
Okay, thanks a lot.
Okay.
All right, thanks.